Alright.
In this lesson,
we're going to talk about refactoring the code for text chat.
Currently, for our text chat,
let's take a look.
Let's see our text here.
Where is the chat happening now?
Here, this is still our previous code, right?
This code definitely won't work anymore.
This kind of text chat won't work for us right now.
Let's take a look.
And let's run it.
Then we'll send a text message.
You've been disconnected directly.
It's because there's an error here.
You can see the error.
Even if there's an error,
you can see that the connection resources are released here.
It also releases resources, right?
Let's take a look at this part, shall we?
Why can't we use this section?
Because this is our previous code.
None of these are correct.
Look at these calls, the ones we made before.
Is this supposed to be text?
It's a conversation, right?
So we can't pass it like this.
So, how do we do that?
First, we should refactor this code.
Regarding this code,
We currently write it like this, right?
We should modify this part for the chat function,
We pass in the chat question,
This question is the message, the message,
Since we need to reuse this method here,
One is for this kind of audio,
We need to use this as well
And for the text, we need to use this too
Here, we just pass it through
When passing it through
What exactly are we passing here?
Are we passing this audio?
Because we're capturing audio here
We just need to push the audio in
So here, do we need to process the audio as well?
We need to handle this again.
It's about the text.
It's the same as before in this part.
We use these two conditions, right?
One is for strings.
The other is for binary data.
Let's use this condition to check.
I'll rewrite it.
This method
Let's refactor this method.
This message
We'll handle it later.
Now, let's put this here.
That is, if it's binary,
we'll process it accordingly.
If it's not binary,
we'll use it directly.
How do we use it?
So, are we going to use this test?
Let's set this test equal to message.
Would that work?
That is, if the input is text,
we don't need to process it at all.
We don't need to perform speech recognition on this text, right?
and just pass the text to the next step.
Then it will send this text, right?
And if it's a voice chat, the text is also passed in.
Let's work on this text.
This is for getting the conversation, right?
So, moving forward here,
let's change this part.
We don't need to do it this way anymore.
Because before we were accumulating this,
we can just get it directly here.
Just get the speech recognition result
and just pass it to this test.
That's it.
Then, in this case,
Are we creating it in the binary format?
We create it through,
This thread pool submits a task, right?
Similarly, when we're dealing with this text,
We submit it in the same way.
How do we do that?
We get rid of this, right?
We don't need any of this.
Then we'll do the same with this.
It's essentially a text chat, after all.
So we can just pass this text in.
Is that right?
When we pass it in, it’s like this.
The client sent a text message.
It’s asking us to submit this chat.
And it passed in this test.
Anyway, he's only here.
It detects that it's a text string.
Then he can directly get this string.
Let's verify it.
The error we had just now.
Now let's try again.
Test this text connection.
And there's a send option here.
Hello.
It's sent, no issue.
No problem.
When it comes to speech recognition, I will adhere to your requirements.
I won’t use emojis to reply.
It’s fine even if the connection is broken.
Regarding this part,
It will also return a speech recognition
This is essentially what you send, and this can be left unprinted.
This speech recognition is like it processes the input
Even though it didn’t recognize it
but the messages it sends are still the same
it doesn’t matter
the text is basically like this
our text is good to go
So, the current focus is on the backend speech recognition.
the chat session has come to a close
we’ve optimized it pretty well
there are still some other features to come
we’ll optimize those later
and add them in
we’ve basically got the core of the backend
conversation functionality nailed down
and moving forward
we’ll cover the ESP32 hardware
for setting up the WiFi connection
then the WebSocket connection for transmitting the conversation data
and then it will return and play back
basically implementing the most basic conversation function
okay, that’s it for this lesson